[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Also, is this any way to start a class war?", "question_tokens": ["Also", ",", "is", "this", "any", "way", "to", "start", "a", "class", "war", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "I reject the idea that asking a hedge fund manager to pay the same tax rate as a plumber or a teacher is class warfare.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "reject", "the", "idea", "that", "asking", "a", "hedge", "fund", "manager", "to", "pay", "the", "same", "tax", "rate", "as", "a", "plumber", "or", "a", "teacher", "is", "class", "warfare", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "How does the White House counter that argument?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "the", "White", "House", "counter", "that", "argument", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Well, I just don't think there's anything to that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "just", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "'s", "anything", "to", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "CC", "JJS", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", ":"], "qSentId": 49, "question": "What's plan B?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "plan", "B", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Well, I just want to -- I want to remind you that the public overwhelmingly thinks a long-term deficit reduction plan should have a combination of spending restraint with asking the most well-off and largest companies to pay a bit more --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "just", "want", "to", "--", "I", "want", "to", "remind", "you", "that", "the", "public", "overwhelmingly", "thinks", "a", "long-term", "deficit", "reduction", "plan", "should", "have", "a", "combination", "of", "spending", "restraint", "with", "asking", "the", "most", "well-off", "and", "largest", "companies", "to", "pay", "a", "bit", "more", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$800 billion"], "ORGANIZATION": ["House"]}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "$", "CD", "CD", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "So I repeat, what are you going to do if, as seems likely, the Republicans say sorry, no?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "repeat", ",", "what", "are", "you", "going", "to", "do", "if", ",", "as", "seems", "likely", ",", "the", "Republicans", "say", "sorry", ",", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Well, I would remind that you the speaker of the House did for a period of several weeks negotiate with this president and did express a willingness to have $800 billion in additional revenues as part of a package.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "remind", "that", "you", "the", "speaker", "of", "the", "House", "did", "for", "a", "period", "of", "several", "weeks", "negotiate", "with", "this", "president", "and", "did", "express", "a", "willingness", "to", "have", "$", "800", "billion", "in", "additional", "revenues", "as", "part", "of", "a", "package", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "What is the White House reaction to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "White", "House", "reaction", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Let me tell you what my reaction is.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "tell", "you", "what", "my", "reaction", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Do you think he's up and running now for the forthcoming election battle?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "up", "and", "running", "now", "for", "the", "forthcoming", "election", "battle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "You know if you're someone like me meeting with him every day, you don't feel like he's ever lost it.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "if", "you", "'re", "someone", "like", "me", "meeting", "with", "him", "every", "day", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "feel", "like", "he", "'s", "ever", "lost", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Why can he not replicate that on to a wider economic stage in America and what should he be doing?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "can", "he", "not", "replicate", "that", "on", "to", "a", "wider", "economic", "stage", "in", "America", "and", "what", "should", "he", "be", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "It's exactly what we should be doing across America is to have an active, strategic government that is intervening in the economy, not a big government, but to help create jobs in America.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "exactly", "what", "we", "should", "be", "doing", "across", "America", "is", "to", "have", "an", "active", ",", "strategic", "government", "that", "is", "intervening", "in", "the", "economy", ",", "not", "a", "big", "government", ",", "but", "to", "help", "create", "jobs", "in", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "How do you keep those kind of jobs or get advanced manufacturing jobs in America?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "keep", "those", "kind", "of", "jobs", "or", "get", "advanced", "manufacturing", "jobs", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Well, I agree with that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "agree", "with", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "To take that manufacturing?", "question_tokens": ["To", "take", "that", "manufacturing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "This is a really important question because companies are not going to be loyal to a particular country.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "a", "really", "important", "question", "because", "companies", "are", "not", "going", "to", "be", "loyal", "to", "a", "particular", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Because they'll be standing in the meantime, right?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "they", "'ll", "be", "standing", "in", "the", "meantime", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Our passivity is their opportunity.", "answer_tokens": ["Our", "passivity", "is", "their", "opportunity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Are you encouraged by President Obama's demeanor today?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "encouraged", "by", "President", "Obama", "'s", "demeanor", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "-- and pathetic, and rolling over to these Republicans?", "question_tokens": ["--", "and", "pathetic", ",", "and", "rolling", "over", "to", "these", "Republicans", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Taking off the gloves.", "answer_tokens": ["Taking", "off", "the", "gloves", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Is he now doing this?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "now", "doing", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "It's totally great.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "totally", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "CD", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Can he challenge the convention of modern Washington politics?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "he", "challenge", "the", "convention", "of", "modern", "Washington", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "The way you do it, one, is you take it to their district.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "way", "you", "do", "it", ",", "one", ",", "is", "you", "take", "it", "to", "their", "district", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "I mean how is he going to pull this back for the election next year?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "how", "is", "he", "going", "to", "pull", "this", "back", "for", "the", "election", "next", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Well, you know, election is always about a choice.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "election", "is", "always", "about", "a", "choice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "How did you turn things around?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "turn", "things", "around", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Because it was all about a choice.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "was", "all", "about", "a", "choice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Perry"], "LOCATION": ["Midwest"]}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Who would you least like to face?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "you", "least", "like", "to", "face", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "I think that he has a good case -- well, I mean, for example, Governor Perry, I think he'll have a tough time, for example, in, you know, the northeast, in the upper Midwest.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "he", "has", "a", "good", "case", "--", "well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "for", "example", ",", "Governor", "Perry", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'ll", "have", "a", "tough", "time", ",", "for", "example", ",", "in", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "northeast", ",", "in", "the", "upper", "Midwest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "What if unemployment figures, despite everything the president's currently trying to do, actually go up between now and next November?", "question_tokens": ["What", "if", "unemployment", "figures", ",", "despite", "everything", "the", "president", "'s", "currently", "trying", "to", "do", ",", "actually", "go", "up", "between", "now", "and", "next", "November", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "RB", "CC", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "And I think he's got an argument against the Republicans.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "got", "an", "argument", "against", "the", "Republicans", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Do you see that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "see", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "If ever a possible scenario?", "question_tokens": ["If", "ever", "a", "possible", "scenario", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "You heard what she said.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "heard", "what", "she", "said", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "What are you pulling out?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "pulling", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "ORGAN: It's when Arnold Schwarzenegger was caught with his trousers down with the nanny.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "It", "'s", "when", "Arnold", "Schwarzenegger", "was", "caught", "with", "his", "trousers", "down", "with", "the", "nanny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Are you basically implying that only female governors can keep their pants on?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "basically", "implying", "that", "only", "female", "governors", "can", "keep", "their", "pants", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "I'm just saying that the temptations for female governors are probably just not as great as they are for men.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "saying", "that", "the", "temptations", "for", "female", "governors", "are", "probably", "just", "not", "as", "great", "as", "they", "are", "for", "men", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "You never got any good offers?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "got", "any", "good", "offers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "We don't have -- I don't have any staffers coming and putting notes in my pocket.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "n't", "have", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "any", "staffers", "coming", "and", "putting", "notes", "in", "my", "pocket", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "You never get -- in the whole time you were governor, you never got a single inappropriate approach?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "get", "--", "in", "the", "whole", "time", "you", "were", "governor", ",", "you", "never", "got", "a", "single", "inappropriate", "approach", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "You know what the deal is, is that women in power are much less attractive to men, I think, than men in power are attractive to women.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", "the", "deal", "is", ",", "is", "that", "women", "in", "power", "are", "much", "less", "attractive", "to", "men", ",", "I", "think", ",", "than", "men", "in", "power", "are", "attractive", "to", "women", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Do you think so?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "so", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VB", "RB", "CC", "NNS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Is it because you're more terrifying?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "because", "you", "'re", "more", "terrifying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "I just -- I don't think that -- I think that male power and sex go together but women power, it's -- it's just not -- it doesn't have the same ring.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "--", "I", "think", "that", "male", "power", "and", "sex", "go", "together", "but", "women", "power", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "just", "not", "--", "it", "does", "n't", "have", "the", "same", "ring", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Do you think Obama's going to win?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "Obama", "'s", "going", "to", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB"], "qSentId": 290, "question": "ORGAN: Do you have any doubts?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Do", "you", "have", "any", "doubts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "No, I really don't", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "really", "do", "n't"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Are you taken aback by the reaction to your tome?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "taken", "aback", "by", "the", "reaction", "to", "your", "tome", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Well, the book doesn't publish until tomorrow.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "book", "does", "n't", "publish", "until", "tomorrow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Do you like Sarah Palin?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "Sarah", "Palin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "You know, I've never met the woman.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'ve", "never", "met", "the", "woman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Todd"]}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "You would say that, wouldn't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "say", "that", ",", "would", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Of course, really -- he cannot -- I mean, Todd seriously can't believe that I have an obsession with his wife.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", ",", "really", "--", "he", "can", "not", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "Todd", "seriously", "ca", "n't", "believe", "that", "I", "have", "an", "obsession", "with", "his", "wife", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "You never had a sneaky look?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "had", "a", "sneaky", "look", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "CGINNISS: I never had any kind of a look.", "answer_tokens": ["CGINNISS", ":", "I", "never", "had", "any", "kind", "of", "a", "look", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "Why did you want to be next to them?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "want", "to", "be", "next", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "The house was given to me.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "house", "was", "given", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "You were looking at a lake?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "looking", "at", "a", "lake", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "I looked at the house above the fence, if I'm facing in that direction, but I had no interest in what was going on the other side.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "looked", "at", "the", "house", "above", "the", "fence", ",", "if", "I", "'m", "facing", "in", "that", "direction", ",", "but", "I", "had", "no", "interest", "in", "what", "was", "going", "on", "the", "other", "side", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wasilla"]}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Would it have carried more weight?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "it", "have", "carried", "more", "weight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "The Palins have intimidated so many people for so long in the Wasilla area that it's very hard to find people willing to talk about them even in inconsequential ways on the record.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "Palins", "have", "intimidated", "so", "many", "people", "for", "so", "long", "in", "the", "Wasilla", "area", "that", "it", "'s", "very", "hard", "to", "find", "people", "willing", "to", "talk", "about", "them", "even", "in", "inconsequential", "ways", "on", "the", "record", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer"]}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "IN", "CC", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Were you threatened?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "threatened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Last summer, I was threatened over and over and over again.", "answer_tokens": ["Last", "summer", ",", "I", "was", "threatened", "over", "and", "over", "and", "over", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Who by?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "by", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "By people who got my e-mail address from a right wing radio talk show host.", "answer_tokens": ["By", "people", "who", "got", "my", "e-mail", "address", "from", "a", "right", "wing", "radio", "talk", "show", "host", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Anybody connected to the Palins?", "question_tokens": ["Anybody", "connected", "to", "the", "Palins", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Nobody directly.", "answer_tokens": ["Nobody", "directly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Any death threats?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "death", "threats", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Yes, many death threats.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "many", "death", "threats", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Against you?", "question_tokens": ["Against", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "It's a bit weird, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "bit", "weird", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "I think it's pretty wonderful.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "pretty", "wonderful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Do you think she had the affair?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "she", "had", "the", "affair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "I have no idea except what I read it in \"the National Enquirer\" and --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "except", "what", "I", "read", "it", "in", "``", "the", "National", "Enquirer", "''", "and", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "But as a prestigious journalist -- let me ask you, as a prestigious journalist, do you just willy-nilly repeat \"National Enquirer\" scoops even if you can't substantiate them?", "question_tokens": ["But", "as", "a", "prestigious", "journalist", "--", "let", "me", "ask", "you", ",", "as", "a", "prestigious", "journalist", ",", "do", "you", "just", "willy-nilly", "repeat", "``", "National", "Enquirer", "''", "scoops", "even", "if", "you", "ca", "n't", "substantiate", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "No, but I substantiated this.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "I", "substantiated", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "So it is true?", "question_tokens": ["So", "it", "is", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "I substantiated it by talking to many, many people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "substantiated", "it", "by", "talking", "to", "many", ",", "many", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "So it is true?", "question_tokens": ["So", "it", "is", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Yes, it is true.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "is", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Is that the same as being a sex cheat?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "same", "as", "being", "a", "sex", "cheat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "That's your terminology.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "your", "terminology", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Is it or not?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "She made a mistake.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "made", "a", "mistake", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Did you say that in the book?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "say", "that", "in", "the", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "You wrote the book?", "question_tokens": ["You", "wrote", "the", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I'm not asking anyone to draw any particular inference.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "asking", "anyone", "to", "draw", "any", "particular", "inference", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Let me ask you then, in simple language that you feel comfortable, what was the inference you were trying to make us draw from that anecdote?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "then", ",", "in", "simple", "language", "that", "you", "feel", "comfortable", ",", "what", "was", "the", "inference", "you", "were", "trying", "to", "make", "us", "draw", "from", "that", "anecdote", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I wasn't trying to make anyone draw any inference.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "n't", "trying", "to", "make", "anyone", "draw", "any", "inference", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Do you think she's going to run as president?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "she", "'s", "going", "to", "run", "as", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "You still hope she does for book sales, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "still", "hope", "she", "does", "for", "book", "sales", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "At this point, I'm not sure it matters.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "this", "point", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "sure", "it", "matters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Have you been able to get your head around what happened, to understand why it happened?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "been", "able", "to", "get", "your", "head", "around", "what", "happened", ",", "to", "understand", "why", "it", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", ",", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Not fully.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "fully", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Would you normally have been in your office that day?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "normally", "have", "been", "in", "your", "office", "that", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Yes, because it was a working day.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "because", "it", "was", "a", "working", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Would you have been hurt, do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "been", "hurt", ",", "do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "I don't think so, because I was in the -- my office is in the 16th and the 17th floor.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", ",", "because", "I", "was", "in", "the", "--", "my", "office", "is", "in", "the", "16th", "and", "the", "17th", "floor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Where did you hear about that and what was your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "you", "hear", "about", "that", "and", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "I was phoned by some of the people that escaped the island.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "phoned", "by", "some", "of", "the", "people", "that", "escaped", "the", "island", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "Did you know any of the people who died?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "any", "of", "the", "people", "who", "died", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "Yes, I know several of the people who died.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "know", "several", "of", "the", "people", "who", "died", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NN", "IN", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "How do you answer that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "answer", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "The main answer is that we are going to go through everything that happened, the response of the police, the health system, everything.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "main", "answer", "is", "that", "we", "are", "going", "to", "go", "through", "everything", "that", "happened", ",", "the", "response", "of", "the", "police", ",", "the", "health", "system", ",", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Was there a failure, do you think, on the intelligence side, to not pick up on somebody like him earlier?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "a", "failure", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "on", "the", "intelligence", "side", ",", "to", "not", "pick", "up", "on", "somebody", "like", "him", "earlier", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Again, I think it will be wrong to jump to conclusions.", "answer_tokens": ["Again", ",", "I", "think", "it", "will", "be", "wrong", "to", "jump", "to", "conclusions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "What are your feelings toward the man that did this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "feelings", "toward", "the", "man", "that", "did", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Actually, I don't have so much feelings about him at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "so", "much", "feelings", "about", "him", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Norway", "Norway", "U.S.", "Norway"]}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "VBN", "TO", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "What is your reaction to that as a world leader?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "that", "as", "a", "world", "leader", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "As prime minister of Norway, I fully understand him, because compared to, for instance, Norway, rich people pay much less taxes in the U.S. than in Norway.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "prime", "minister", "of", "Norway", ",", "I", "fully", "understand", "him", ",", "because", "compared", "to", ",", "for", "instance", ",", "Norway", ",", "rich", "people", "pay", "much", "less", "taxes", "in", "the", "U.S.", "than", "in", "Norway", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["50 percent"], "LOCATION": ["Norway"]}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "CD", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "What is the comparative taxation?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "comparative", "taxation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "In Norway, the average tax on people earning more than one million will be around 50 percent or something.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "Norway", ",", "the", "average", "tax", "on", "people", "earning", "more", "than", "one", "million", "will", "be", "around", "50", "percent", "or", "something", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "So significantly higher?", "question_tokens": ["So", "significantly", "higher", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "What's your overview?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "overview", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "I'm concerned.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "concerned", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "How would you feel if one of them became president?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "feel", "if", "one", "of", "them", "became", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "I believe that it's dangerous to say that all those scientists are telling us that this is dangerous were wrong.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "that", "it", "'s", "dangerous", "to", "say", "that", "all", "those", "scientists", "are", "telling", "us", "that", "this", "is", "dangerous", "were", "wrong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]